I'm back.
W-Welcome back!
Thank you.
I'll email you the receipts.
Thank you very much!
Do you think we'll be able to
get copy paper restocked?
Yes, they said it should be fine!
Thank you.
It's been a week since we started dating.
I want to have more...
lovey-dovey moments with Tonome-san!
YAKO TONOME
Say ah!
Oh, I'm all drunk!
You're adorable.
No one will see us here.
I-Is he gonna smooch me?!
I know we promised to keep our private
lives separate from work, but...
Things just happened
to get really busy at work!
We do work together, after all...
Y-Yes, of course!
I'm so embarrassed, getting
distracted like this!
Meanwhile, Tonome-san
is completely focused on his work!
Very well.
I, too, shall become a demon for work!
I hereby swear to seal
away my lovey-dovey urges!
SPLASH
Yako-san.
What is it, sir?!
Is something the matter?
N-No!
More work? Lay it on me!
Listen... Things
have been so busy lately,
would it be all right to set our
promise aside for just a moment?
I'm sorry to burden you
with my impatience.
I-I've actually...
Should we go somewhere for the weekend?
Yes...
I'd just gone and hardened
my heart, too!
But you need punishment
for breaking your promise.
Y-Yako-san... please...
Is this really necessary?!
Tickle tickle tickle...
Can I go in yet?
Yako-san.
Yes?
I'll be signing out early today.
I can see you home.
Thank you for seeing me back.
Of course. I'll see you tomorrow.
W-Wait...
Would you like to share a cup of tea?!
All right.
Please do.
All right. I'll call a taxi.
Wait!
I thought maybe...
we could walk together.
What do you think?
Of course we can.
We're waiting to serve you!
H-Hey... Tonome-san?
Yes, the train is coming.
I want...
Operation Share a Cup of Tea,
Take 2, to go perfectly!
I also had my mom check my room
for cleanliness three days ago!
Yeah, it's nice and clean!
Thank goodness! Thanks!
I also put my laundry away.
You're clear! Don't worry!
Will you invite me in for tea again?
Or would you prefer another day?
I-I'll make all kinds of tea!
I'm glad to hear it.
I even bought sweets for us.
I can't wait to try them.
I'll make the tea, so please sit down.
Let me help you!
Absolutely not.
You're the guest.
Of course.
That's right.
I cleaned up recently,
but if I missed anything, I'm sorry.
It's perfectly clean.
Thank goodness!
Sometimes I drop things
and don't notice.
That does sound troubling.
Wh-What do I do? And
why underwear, of all things?
If you see anything
on the floor, let me know!
I can't tell her this.
I'll just try not to stare.
Tonome-san, where are you sitting?
Th-The chair across from you.
I'll come get it from you.
Don't you worry! I'm on my way!
Did I spill any?
No, not at all!
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
It's probably safest
to pretend I didn't see...
But there's no telling
when she may realize it's there.
There's also a chance someone else
could come by and see it first.
I have to find a way to let her know
without hurting her!
Time to use my detective
skills to their fullest!
What's this here?
Looks like a handkerchief.
Yes, it is a handkerchief!
Shall we have the sweets?
I have my tea already.
Y-Yes!
It's delicious!
Very nice.
What is?
Oh, just...
I'm always invisible,
so it takes about two seconds for things
that enter my body
to become invisible too.
I see.
It feels rude to let
people see me chewing,
so I tend to have to wait
for it to become invisible first.
I see!
When I was a kid,
my parents told me not to chew
with my mouth open.
I'm sometimes jealous of people
who can enjoy their food with abandon.
In that case, feel free to eat
as quickly as you want in front of me!
I can't see it anyway!
Wait, you should have said
"because we're dating!"
But it's embarrassing
to say it outright...
I still don't fully feel like
Tonome-san and I are a couple...
W-Well, then...
I-Is it good?
I feel like I've done
something offensive.
You've internalized it, huh?
Tonome-san, be careful on your way home.
I will. Thank you for the delicious tea.
Finding my undies
on the floor was embarrassing...
I'm just glad Tonome-san thought
they were a handkerchief!
That reminds me...
Shall we use first names
when in private together?
W-Well... the thought makes me blush.
Yes, I feel the same way.
Shizuka-san.
I'm not used to it yet!
Don't say it so often.
That was just twice.
Stop that, now!
Tonome-san, are you still here?
Yes, you are.
Wh-What is it?
I'm sorry.
You're just so charming,
I was thinking about kissing you.
Sighted and visible people make eye
contact to judge the timing of a kiss,
but I realize that's not
possible for either of us.
H-How should we do it, then?
Should we come up with a signal?
Oh? Does that mean I can kiss you?
Did you just touch my forehead?
I did.
Jarashi-san, could you handle this?
On it!
Kikira-san, how's the research coming?
Tonome-san, did something nice happen?
There's a spring in your step
and in your voice.
Actually, I just got a new suit!
Hey, yeah. Never seen that one before.
Does it look good on me?
How should I know? You're invisible, man.
Well, I suppose...
I can hear in his voice that he's hurt!
I want to help, but
I don't know about clothes!
I dunno squat about clothes,
but it's got a good vibe.
Hey, good point! The vibe!
Yeah, it suits you well, in that sense.
And the dull green color
is nice and different.
That's right! I really liked the color!
I get it now!
You've both got great taste.
I can't participate in this topic,
but I'm glad that he's so happy.
Yako-san.
I think the suit fabric
has a nice feel, too.
Would you like to touch it?
It feels very nice!
It sure does! Soft, right?
You're so cute today! Like a little boy!
You're embarrassing me.
Do you like fashion, Tonome-san?
I'm not sure about fashion,
but I do like clothes.
It's the only way I can
express myself, after all.
Speaking of, I've been wondering.
The thing where invisible people
make their clothing invisible...
How does that work?
It appears our bodies produce a substance
that makes us invisible.
Full invisibility is like...
We can flip a switch in our bodies
to turn it on and off.
Doesn't make sense to me.
If we held hands,
would my hand disappear too?
Shall we try it?
It doesn't work
on living things, of course.
He linked his fingers in mine!
Sure must be nice
to be invisible, though!
Real convenient!
Though legally, we're not allowed to
use full invisibility in public spaces.
For real?
Yes.
I do have a special license
for it for my job,
but when I'm invisible on the street,
people tend to bump into me,
so I avoid it in public when possible.
It can be quite dangerous.
I'm picking up what he's laying down!
Welcome!
Oh! It's been a while, Yako-san.
Hello!
I brought my mother today.
What a lovely shop!
Hello! I'm Shizuka's mother!
My daughter says she loved your shop!
Really? I'm so happy to have you.
I've never made my own tea before!
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you!
I wonder if Yako-san has told her
about Tonome-san yet.
She told me recently that they
are officially dating, but...
Sup!
Light-san! Karma-san!
Hello!
Nice to see ya!
I'm sorry about all that trouble before.
It's teacake. I hope
you'll enjoy it together.
Oh, thank you very much!
Thank you. Please join us for tea.
I'll make it now.
Hey, hey, Yako-chan!
I hear you and Tonome-chan are official?
Hey! Don't talk about
that in their workplace!
Yeah.
Turbo cute! I'm fallin' for her myself!
Ow, ow, ow! I'm sorry!
She may not have told her,
so I should probably avoid mentioning him.
Hey, it's Yako-chan!
You and the BF hitched yet?
Hey!
Marriage is a long way off for her.
Aw, for reals?
It's okay, then?
It's much too soon for that!
Elves may be long-lived,
but humans have a different sense of time!
I do wonder what her boyfriend is like!
He's one transparent guy,
I can tell you that much!
Well, that much is true...
I can't wait to meet him!
But I had no idea!
So Shizuka has a boyfriend now?
Let me meet him sometime!
S-Sure...
Do you have that information
yet, Shizu— Yako-san?
Aki— Tonome-san, I just sent it to you.
Just use your first names already, man.
They're probably trying
to keep it out of the workplace.
It's not our place to comment on it.
That's their call,
but it's just so dang obvious!
Yet if I ask, they deflect.
You guys official yet?!
That's a secret!
Having to dance around it
is just exhausting for everyone.
Fair point.
Hey, you two.
It's obvious that you're dating,
so call each other what you want.
Sheesh.
Didn't you just say it wasn't our place?!
I'm tired of dancing around it!
Um...
I feel kind of bad...
H-Hey, it's fine!
Nothing for you to apologize for!
If you want to hide it,
try harder!
Sheesh.
Kikira! Have a little tact!
What else was I supposed to say?
Come in.
Hello. Is now a good time?
Oh, Madaraito-san.
I've got a job for you!
MEETING ROOM
It's about a case I'm working on.
Right.
I'd like to get some information
that will help my client.
I'll come by with my
client in the future,
so you can get the details from them.
Of course. I understand.
I'll see you soon, then.
By the way, Tonome-san!
Yes?
I love the color of your suit today!
Y-You get it?!
Yes! I'd love to try out
more things like that,
but we lawyers don't get to
play around with our fashion.
I'm jealous.
What about getting adventurous
with pocket squares and accessories?
That's perfect!
Tonome-san, you're brilliant!
Madaraito-san's such a cheerful man.
He always notices little things
to praise about me.
Well, everyone, good luck with your work!
I left a souvenir with Tonome-san!
Thank you for coming!
I hope there's a Churun in there!
Got it! I'll remember that for next time.
Please don't.
Well, be careful on your way home.
Tonome-san.
Thanks for always looking after us.
O-Of course.
Your law offices have been
a great help to us, too.
Eh?
Hey, Daichi.
Haven't you told your agency
that I'm your partner?
I just assumed they all knew.
Do I gotta tell 'em?
I'd like them to call me if
something happens to you at work!
We see each other at work too.
It's important to make a good impression.
We'll tell 'em then. Sheesh.
I'm coming back to
Tonome-san's agency next week.
So we'll do it then.
We'd better!
I get it already.
Sheesh.
Anyway, this guy's my partner.
Thanks for taking such
good care of my Daichi!
Madaraito-san?!
CHURUN
And here. For you!
Thanks a bunch!
Hey, what do you even see in Kikira?
You're going there?
We started dating in high school.
In the mountains—
Hey.
You did what you came for, so leave.
Sorry. Daichi hates mixing his work
and his private life.
I'll leave it at that for now.
The mountains.
I'm so curious.
You'll catch a cold.
Akira-san!
Shizuka-san. How are you feeling?
I was thinking of dropping by...
I-It's just a cold, really!
But...
I would like... if you were here...
I'll be there right away.
Goodbye.
I let him spoil me!
It's easy to catch cold
when the seasons change!
Thanks for coming.
I'll handle the housework,
so you take it easy.
'Kay.
I forgot my mom was here!
Mom, that phone call was...
Mom?
Huh, she's not here?
Did she go home?
C-Coming!
You really did come right by!
I happened to be close by when I called.
I can't catch human colds,
so you don't need to wear a mask.
Really?
Yes.
Here, I'll make you something.
Really?!
You need egg rice porridge
at times like these!
My favorite!
The sounds of Akira-san cooking...
The egg rice porridge is finished.
Smells delicious! I assume, anyway...
It's hard when you've got
a stuffy nose, yeah.
Here you are.
It's hot, so be careful.
R-Right!
Let's eat!
Yako-san?
Um... could you feed me... maybe?
Yeah, maybe that's a little too far...
Oh, I don't mind.
I'll blow on it, too.
N-No!
You don't have to do that!
Shizuka-san. Open your mouth.
Say ah.
Ah...
Was it too hot?
These are convulsions of joy!
May I?
Wait, did he just get on my bed?!
You had rice on your face.
Wh-Who are you?!
I'm Shizuka's mother!
Mother?!
I'm so sorry! I was hanging out the wash!
I was trying to stay hidden
so I didn't interrupt, but...
Just give me a minute
to get out of your hair, okay?
You don't have to go!
Actually, I'm sorry
I didn't introduce myself...
Not at all! Have fun!
EPISODE 3: DATING FOR A WEEK
TO BE CONTINUED